nice to meet you.
初めまして
It's cute.
かわいいですね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Your smile is nice too.
笑顔もいいですね
It's charming too.
愛嬌もいいですね
Isn't it a perfect score of 100?
100点満点じゃないですか
It's very thin.
めっちゃ細いですね
Is it true?
本当ですか?
What are you doing?
何かしてるの?
normally.
普段
Are you careful?
気をつけてるんですか?
surely.
たしかに
This is just a little bit.
多少だけこれなんだ
For example, maybe a massage?
例えば、マッサージしたりとか?
Do you want a massage?
マッサージするの?
Do you have leg problems?
足問題とかして?
Great.
えらい
Her skin is also white.
肌も白いですね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
it is?
それは?
Are you doing something?
何かやってるの?
Things like skin.
肌とか
My skin is protected from the sun.
肌は日焼け止めになってます
Don't want to burn?
焼けたくない?
I don't want to burn.
焼 けたくない
While taking a camera.
カメラ撮りながら
In front of the camera
カメラの前で、
first time?
初 めて?
Are you nervous?
緊張してる?
I'm nervous.
緊張してます
You said you were nervous, but
緊張してるって言ってくれたけど、
I think you're nervous, I think you're nervous,
緊 張してると思うから、 バクバクしてると思うから、
While chatting about various things and blowfishing,
いろいろおしゃべりしながら、 フグしながら、
I guess I'll do it.
やっていこうかな
What do you usually do?
普段は何してるんですか?
I usually work part-time at a cafe.
普段はカフェでバイトしてます
Cafe?
カ フェ?
Is that what it feels like?
そんな感じ?
Can you remember?
覚えれるんですか?
Can you understand if I ask?
聞いたら分かるの?
Even Kon-chan.
こんちゃんでも
I'll try it now, so take a guess.
俺今やってみるから、 当ててみて
Are you saying?
言ってます?
I've never said that before, so I don't know if I'm guessing.
言ったことないから、 当ててるのか分かんなかったけど
I'm sure you'll have quite a few encounters at cafes, right?
カフェとかだと、結構出会いとかあるんじゃないですか?
No, not at all.
いや、全然ないです
Not at all?
全然ないの?
Don't you have a boyfriend?
彼氏いないの?
There aren't any.
いないですよ
Very close.
めっちゃ近い
I'm not there.
いないです
How long have you been gone?
どれくらいいないの?
I've never been able to do it.
できたことないです
Have you never been able to do it?
できたことないんですか?
why?
なんで?
There was a rare one, right?
レアあったでしょ?
Just a little bit.
ちょっとね
Does that mean you have no experience?
経験自体はないってこと?
I have experience.
経験はあります
Maybe it's better not to ask.
聞かないほうがいいかもしれない
Does that mean you have little experience?
経験薄いってこと?
Not that much.
そんなにはないですね
I've never dated him, but he's someone I like.
付き合ったことはないけど、 自分が好きな人で、
We were trying to date, but I don't think we ever got that far.
付き合おうとしてたんだけど、 そこまで至らなかったって感じだ
Right.
よね
Somehow.
なん となく
Donpisha.
ドンピシャ
I'll stop talking about this.
この話はやめときます
Do you have any hobbies?
趣味とかあるんですか?
hobby...
趣味...
I read manga.
漫画とか読んでます
What series do you read?
何系読むの?
various...
いろいろ...
What is it?
なんだろう?
Attack on Titan?
進撃の巨人?
It's quite like that.
結構そういうの
I read boys' books.
少年系読むんですね
Juvenile type?
少年系?
Lately I've been into backgrounds.
最近は背景にハマってますね
It's popular.
人気ですよ
I like the gap.
ギャップがいいですよね
There are various character personalities.
いろいろキャラの個性とかもあって
It has a pretty serious feel, so it's like a spot-on type.
結構シリアスな感じから、 スポッコン系とか
It looked quite wide.
結構幅広く見えたんですね
What do you do on your day off?
お休みの日は何してる?
On my day off...I read manga.
休みの日...漫画読んでます
Maybe my days off and my hobbies are linked.
休みの日と趣味が連動してるかも
that's right.
そう です
Are you an Indian type?
インドタイプですか?
It's really indoors.
ガッツリインドアですね
Going outside?
外に出ること?
To go outside.
外に出ること
Dinner with friends.
友達とご飯
I guess it's just shopping.
ショッピングしたりぐらいですかね
On that day...
その日は...
To die.
死ぬこと
Do it like this.
こう やって
Well, it's white.
まあ、白いもんね
that's right.
そうです
I see.
なるほどね
I don't have a boyfriend right now.
今、彼氏がいないと
I have never done it before.
やっていたことないと
What kind of people are there?
どういう人がたくさんいるの?
The main premise is to be kind.
大前提として、優しい
kind.
優しい
Younger, older.
年下、お年上だと
If anything, he's older.
どちらかと言えば、年上
Up to what age can I go?
何歳ぐらいまでいけるんですか?
If you like it, click here.
好きになった人は、ここ
In terms of appearance, what kind of person are you?
見た目で言うと、どういう人かって
I wonder what it is.
なんだろうな
A person with a sense of cleanliness.
清潔感のある人
Oh, you're being lied to.
え、ごまかされてる
It's so deceiving.
すげえごまかされてる
Okay, now that I've gotten to my boyfriend, where do you want to go?
じゃあ、彼氏にまで行ったら、 どこ行きたい?
First date.
初デート
A first date, or rather, an ideal date.
初デートっていうか、理想のデート
An ideal date.
理想のデート
My ideal date would be at home.
理想のデートは、家で居たい
We were relaxing and hanging out.
まったりして、くっついたりしてて
Just like that.
そのままね
That's good.
いいっすね
Like, already, already.
もう、もう、みたいな
to this point.
ここまで
My boyfriend is also watching.
彼氏もご視聴中です
Well then, yes.
じゃあ、そうですね
I've been doing a lot of things, but I just can't resist.
いろいろしてたんですけど、我慢できないんで
I can see it, but it's not very clear.
見 えるんですけど、 ぽっきりしないですよ
It won't look bulky.
ぽっきりしないですよ
amazing.
すごい
That's it.
あれだね
It's my first time.
初めてね
It's cute.
かわいいね
I can see it.
見えてるね
difficult.
難しい
I can see it.
見えてるもんね
That's difficult.
難しいね
It's my first time.
初めてね
take off your pants
パンツを脱いで
hey.
ね
Take your clothes off.
脱 いでよ
Get on your knees.
膝立ちして
Kneel.
膝立ち